(Howard:)Why don't we go fool
around in our bedroom?
(Howard:)And then you
can go shopping.
(Leonard:)I thought maybe after we eat,
we could see an early movie.
(Priya:)I'd love that.
(Leonard:)I love the way you say,
"I'd love that."
(Raj:)She says it the same way I do.
(Raj:)Everybody in India
says it that way.
(Raj:)It's not a big deal.
(Priya:)Rajesh, don't be a child.
(Raj:)I'm not being a child.
(Raj:)Leonard, I swear to God,
(Raj:)if your sister
ever comes to town,
(Raj:)I shall have my way with her.
(Leonard:)My sister's 38 and married.
(Raj:)All the more shame
that will fall
(Raj:)upon the house of Hofstadter.
(Penny:)Ooh, I thought I smelled pizza.
(Sheldon:)That's remarkable.
(Sheldon:)If pepperoni
were an explosive substance,
(Sheldon:)you could replace
German shepherds
(Sheldon:)at our nation's airports.
(Priya:)Hi. Penny, right?
Oh, yes. H-Hi. I'm sorry.